Alyssa DeMartinis

Full-Stack Software Engineer

alyssadee@outlook.com | GitHub | LinkedIn

I'm a full-stack software developer with a background in data entry and customer service. Through my data entry experience I've acquired exceptional attention to detail. My unique job history has taught me to be adaptable in any work environment. I possess a natural curiosity to understand how things work, which has compelled me to be self-motivated and autodidactic.

SKILLS

- Languages and Frameworks: JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS, React, Node, Express, Mongoose, Django
- Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- Management and Deployment: Git, GitHub, Command Line, Visual Studio, Docker

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Immersive | General Assembly | Remote | August 2022 – November 2022 Successfully completed 400+ hours of expert-led instruction in JavaScript frameworks, databases, programming languages and hands-on learning of programming fundamentals and the industry's most in demand technologies. Developed projects, including:

- <u>Create-A-Corgi</u>: A fun app where users can create their own corgi and add it to a database. Built with Mongoose, Express, Node, CSS, Google OAuth
- Werk: An app to track your job applications and skill progress while job searching. Created with a team using Mongoose, Express, React, Node, CSS
- Slots of Terror: Slot machine game with a spooky twist. Built with HTML, JavaScript, CSS

Dealer Tag Agency | Tampa, FL | March 2019–August 2022

Lead EFS Specialist May 2021-August 2022

- Managed Tesla's account of up to 600 deals per day; one of the top grossing dealerships
- Implemented a standard operating procedure to recover workload during busy times of the year
- Distributed the daily workload of EFS deals amongst the employees

Automotive Title Clerk March 2019-May 2021

- Reviewed over 150 vehicle titles per day, equivalent to 20% of all electronic titles processed
- Inquired with dealerships regarding incomplete/incorrect title work and provided notable customer service
- Provided expert knowledge to dealerships regarding the FL DMV regulations and requirements for title work

The Florida Aquarium | Tampa, FL | June 2018—August 2019

Horticultural Assistant August 2018-August 2019

- Maintained and watered the wetlands dome, while providing enrichment for the fish and animals
- Renovated and replanted the front garden to become an educational display of FL native plants
- Created two hanging herb planters out of PVC pipe as enrichment for the lemur exhibit

Horticulture Internship June 2018-August 2018

- Specialized in local mangrove restoration by planting over 50 seedlings
- Participated in 5 beach clean-up events surrounding the bay area

Boston Market | Temple Terrace, FL | January 2008–February 2018 **Shift Supervisor** August 2012-February 2018

- Led a team of 8 people through night shifts and holiday season
- Tracked and maintained 5 proteins on an hourly schedule to ensure adequate product through peak hours
- Ensured cash drawers and safe balanced between shift change and at the end of the day

Cashier/Drive-thru January 2008-August 2012

- Provided exceptional customer service
- Advertised and upsold all featured menu items

EDUCATION

General Assembly | Software Engineering Immersive | Remote
University of South Florida | BS Environmental Biology | Temple Terrace, FL